fulfillmen.com 2017-12-18

# Order Fulfillment Services in China Privacy Policies

## Privacy Policy

Fulfillmen is a China-based company providing cloud-basedwarehouse management. We provide shipping from China to anywhere in the world. 

We are extremely dedicated and committed towards our clients and their privacy. The personal information we collect from our clients is strictly not disclosed.The information is used by our company and team for transaction and business purpose only.

By agreeing to our privacy policy of warehousing and shipment, theclient is liable to provide the required information to keep up with the transactions smoothly.

We ensure that all the products and drop shipping details that are provided to us while you create an account are only used by affiliated and related companies associated with Fulfillmen.

## How Fulfillmen uses your information?

When you are sharing your personal information with us; you have all the right to know how we are going to use it. Here is how we use your information to make warehousing experience better for you.

  1. To maintain your privacy rights
  2. To keep you updated with our Warehouse Management System
  3. To process your transaction hassle free
  4. To provide better customer service

The client’s IP address might be shared with few other affiliated companies in order to send promotional advertisements which can be beneficial to them. In case they do not want such ads, they can always notify us via email or written document to stop the same.

## The information that client needs to provide us

Fulfillmen only collects information that we need to use for customer’s authentic identification.This includes your name, email address, phone number, IP address, residential or office address (place of shipment).

## With whom we share your information?

We do not share your information with any third party who is not related to the business. Certain information is revealed to third parties who are partners with Fulfillmen.Thisis mainly done with the drop shipping companies with whom we have tie-ups.

The other purposes for sharing your information 

  1. To provide promotional offers
  2. Business transfer and financial transaction
  3. To ensure protection of Fulfillmen’s terms and conditionof shipment transaction

Information might also be sharedwith the law enforcement or government officials in cases of illegal, offensive activities or other regulatory administrative issues.Fulfillmenmight also share your data as per requirement if there are court orders and other legal processes. In case some uncanny activity takes place,we reserve the right to disclose data to prevent against potential or actual claims.

## Our policy regarding cookies: 

We at times send very few cookies just to keep track of your user information, shopping cart and tracking of shipment. Our highly qualified IT expertsuse API and WMS software to keep updated with the best techniques to maintain a user-friendly process.

## Our Amendments

Fulfillmen can mold or change this policy at any time as per need. In that case, clients will receive prior notification via mail and also in their registered contact number. 

If you have any further query regarding our privacy policy of warehouse management, feel free to contact and get your query solved.
